Guide to the New Deal in Montana/Fort Peck Dam Oral History Project 1987-1989
Montana Historical Society Research Center
1987-1989
Montana Historical Society Archives
New Deal in Montana/Fort Peck Dam Oral History Project
Montana Historical Society
Sound Recording
122 interviews
Number of pages in transcript or summary provided in container list
This oral history project examines the effects of the New Deal, and the experiences of those involved in the construction of Fort Peck Dam.
Project History
This oral history project documented the economic recovery programs initiated by President Franklin D. Roosevelt in the 1930s and 1940s. These Depression-era programs - including the Work Projects Administration (WPA), Civilian Conservation Corps (CCC), and the resettlement Administration - played a significant economic role in the state of Montana, which was listed as second in per capita receipt of New Deal dollars during the Depression. A large portion of the interviews focused on the lives of the workers involved in the Fort Peck Dam project, including cultural and social life in the area.
The project, conducted between 1987 and 1989, includes 122 interviews with people involved in agricultural programs, commerce, cultural development, Native American culture, labor, work projects, or state and county government. A large portion of the interviews focused on the lives of the workers involved in the Fort Peck Dam project, including cultural and social life in the area.
Inventory is arranged by item, with each oral history interview listed by its unique OH number. An abstract for each interview is provided in the inventory to allow keyword searchability. The abstract includes the number of cassettes, CDs or transcript pages for the interview, as appropriate. Researchers requesting copies of interviews should refer to the OH number when ordering.
To access digital copies of interview audio and transcripts/summaries online, visit Voice of Labor Oral History Collection.
Restrictions, if applicable, are indicated within specific oral history descriptions.
Interviews in the collection conducted by Montana Historical Society Staff or volunteers.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the Montana Historical Society Research Center catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search under these terms.
Montana; Fort Peck Dam (Mont.); New Deal, 1933-1939; United States. Work Projects Administration (Mont.); Civilian Conservation Corps (U.S.)
Montana
Montana; Home and family; Labor history; Oral histories; Sound recordings; Public works; Sports and Recreation
- MADELIA JONES, DOROTHY DEWEY SMITH, AND DORIS JEFFRIES INTERVIEW, OH 1051; 1 tape(s), Summary 5 pages
  Madelia Jones (b. 1905), Dorothy Dewey Smith (b. 1926), and Doris Jeffries lived in the Fort Peck, Montana, area during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s. They discuss their work in the hospital at Wheeler, their childhoods, a tick fever epidemic, their parents' work. Interviewed by Laurie Mercier, August 1, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- KENNETH TURNER, MARJORIE PEARSON TURNER, AND BARBARA PEARSON KAISER INTERVIEW, OH 1052; 1 tape(s), Summary 4 pages
  Kenneth and Marjorie Turner and Barbara Kaiser were residents of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s. They discuss the operation of Hotel Wheeler; their work in the project barracks and mess hall; and recreation. Interviewed by Laurie Mercier, August 1, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- WALTER INLOW INTERVIEW, OH 1053; 1 tape(s), Summary 4 pages
  Walter Inlow (b. 1913) was a resident of Fort Peck, Montana during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam (1936-1939). He discusses dredge work on the dam, working conditions, hardships, recreation. Interviewed by Laurie Mercier, August 1, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- CARTER V. JOHNSON INTERVIEW, OH 1054; 1 tape(s), Summary 5 pages
  Carter V. Johnson was a resident of Fort Peck, Montana during the construction of Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s. He discusses his work as an electrician on the project, recreation, living quarters, construction safety, working conditions. Interviewed by Laurie Mercier, August 1, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- PETER PENNER INTERVIEW, OH 1055; 1 tape(s), Summary 4 pages
  Peter Penner (b. 1892), a resident of Fort Peck, Montana during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s discusses his work as a laborer, work on dredge and sawmill crews, life at Park Grove, the slide disaster. Interviewed by Laurie Mercier, August 1, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- WILLARD C. "CRAIG" SAXTON INTERVIEW, OH 1056; 3 tape(s), Summary 12 pages
  Willard "Craig" Saxton (b. 1914), a resident of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam, discusses his work on the dam, hazards, tunnel construction, his interest in the paleontology of the area, recreation, the secrets of dance hall girls, the nature of work crew, living quarters. Interviewed by Laurie Mercier, July 31, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- VERN AND GUSTAV EMANUELSON INTERVIEW, OH 1057; 1 tape(s), Summary 4 pages
  Vern Emanuelson and Gustav Emanuelson (b. 1909) were residents of Fort Peck, Montana during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s. Gustav discusses working in the tunnels, and road building for the Work Progress Administration (WPA). They both discuss living conditions, and recreation in the area. Interviewed by Laurie Mercier, July 28, 1987, Saco, MT.
- IVER MARTIN INTERVIEW, OH 1058; 2 tape(s), Summary 7 pages
  Iver Martin (b. 1913) was a resident of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s. He discusses driving trucks and buses for the project; the slide disaster; his work at a Civilian Conservation Corps (CCC) camp in Troy; wages; and a visit by President Franklin D. Roosevelt. Interviewed by Laurie Mercier, July 27, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- ROY DEDOBBLELEER INTERVIEW, OH 1059; 2 tape(s), Summary 5 pages
  Roy DeDobbleleer (b. 1907) was a resident of Fort Peck, Montana during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s. He recalls work as a laborer and a pneumatic drill operator; living conditions; farming; employment in other states and Costa Rica. Interviewed by Laurie Mercier, July 27, 1987
- JACK SCHYE INTERVIEW, OH 1060; 1 tape(s), Summary 3 pages
  Jack Schye (b. 1913), a resident of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s remembers the towns of Park Grove and Wheeler; working in the shafts; and recreation. Interviewed by Laurie Mercier, July 27, 1987
- LLOYD LARSON INTERVIEW, OH 1061; 2 tape(s), Summary 7 pages
  Lloyd Larson (b. 1908) was a resident of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s. He discusses his work as a saw operator, the slide disaster, construction accidents, work for the Bowen Garage and living in Glasgow and Wheeler. Interviewed by Laurie Mercier, July 26, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- NORENE ROMIG BROWN INTERVIEW, OH 1062; 1 tape(s), Transcript in-process pages
  Norene Brown (b. 1917) was a Fort Peck, Montana resident during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s. She discusses her work at Vornholt's Drug Store, recreation, dances, living quarters, the slide disaster, living in Glasgow and her husband's work on the dam. Interviewed by Laurie Mercier, July 26, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- CARL H. PLUMLEE INTERVIEW, OH 1063; 2 tape(s), Summary 8 pages
  Carl Plumlee (b. 1909), resident of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s, discusses his schooling at Bozeman, work for the Montana Power Company, surveying, construction problems, building dredges, living conditions. Interviewed by Laurie Mercier, July 31, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- LEONARD BOWSER INTERVIEW, OH 1064; 1 tape(s), Summary 3 pages
  Leonard Bowser (b. 1911) resident of Fork Peck, Montana during the 1930s discusses his work mapping the Fort Peck Dam site; living conditions for workers and their families; a slide disaster; surveying tunnels. Interviewed by Laurie Mercier, July 31, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- THELMA STEARNS BONDY INTERVIEW, OH 1065; 1 tape(s), Transcript 21 pages
  Thelma Bondy (b. 1914) discusses life in Fort Peck, Montana during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the 1930s. She also comments on Martinville, work at the hotel and store, a slide disaster and the flood of 1935. Interviewed by Laurie Mercier, July 31, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- OLAF H. "OLIE" GILBERTSON INTERVIEW, OH 1066; 1 tape(s), Summary 4 pages
  Olaf Gilbertson (b. 1919), a resident of Fort Peck, Montana during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s, discusses living conditions, area towns, recreation, the slide disaster, conducting soil samples, truck driving. Interviewed by Laurie Mercier, July 30, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- ROBERT TAYLOR AND STELLA CLARK TAYLOR INTERVIEW, OH 1067; 1 tape(s), Summary 4 pages
  Robert Taylor (b. 1920) and Stella Clark Taylor were residents of the Fort Peck, Montana area during construction of the Fort Peck Dam during the late 1930s. They discuss Robert's work as surveyor and engineering technician; living in Park Grove; living conditions in the Fort Peck area. Interviewed by Laurie Mercier, July 26, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- ERICK OLSON INTERVIEW, OH 1068; 2 tape(s), Summary 9 pages
  Erick Olson (b. 1907) a resident of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s discusses his work as a tractor operator building a pipeline, barracks life, recreation, wages, hours, an injury to his leg. Interviewed by Laurie Mercier, July 28, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- WILBUR BRYSON INTERVIEW, OH 1069; 1 tape(s),Summary 4 pages
  Wilbur Bryson, (b. 1918) a Fort Peck, Montana resident during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s, discusses barracks life, work hours, recreation, work on the spillway gates and cut-off wall. Interviewed by Laurie Mercier, July 28, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- MELVIN L. HANSON INTERVIEW, OH 1070; 1 tape(s), Transcript 24 pages
  Melvin Hanson (b. 1918) was a resident of Fort Peck, Montana during construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s. He discusses his work as a railroad fireman and engineer for the project on the Saco Branch Line, quarry work at Snake Butte, recreation, and living conditions. Interviewed by Laurie Mercier, July 28, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- RUTH SHANAHAN VAN FAASEN, OH 1071; 1 tape(s), Summary 2 pages
  Ruth Van Faasen (b. 1913), a resident of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s, discusses her work in the accounting office; living in a hotel; recreation. Interviewed by Mary Murphy, August 3, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- ROBERT RHODES INTERVIEW, OH 1072; 1 tape(s), Summary 3 pages
  Robert Rhodes (b. 1903), a resident of Fort Peck, Montana during construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s, discusses work on a dredge crew; his fellow workers; a slide disaster. Interviewed by Mary Murphy, August 2, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- CHARLES "CHUCK" JOHNSTON INTERVIEW, OH 1073; 1 tape(s), Summary 4 pages
  Charles "Chuck" Johnston (1915-1988) was a resident of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s. He discusses dredge work on the dam, photography, the Fort Peck Flying Service, area towns, recreation, living conditions and his later navy career. Interviewed by Mary Murphy, August 2, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- KERMIT BAECKER INTERVIEW, OH 1074; 2 tape(s), Summary 6 pages
  Kermit Baecker (b. 1909) was a resident of Fort Peck, Montana during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s. He discusses his work as a deck hand, moving floating equipment on the Missouri River; wages; living in Wheeler; recreation; slide disaster. Interviewed by Mary Murphy, July 31, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- DAVID GREGG, WILLIAM WHISENNAND, AND LYLE NELSON INTERVIEW, OH 1075; 2 tape(s), Summary 7 pages
  David Gregg (b. 1918), William Whisennand (b. 1916), and Lyle Nelson were residents of Fort Peck, Montana during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam during the late 1930s. They discuss the New Deal Era, raising vegetables, the slide disaster, living conditions, recreation, work on the dam. Interviewed by Mary Murphy, August 1, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- LLOYD CARLSON INTERVIEW, OH 1076; 1 tape(s), Summary 4 pages
  Lloyd Carlson, Fort Peck, Montana resident during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s, discusses his work in the tunnels and as a truck driver; working conditions; recreation; his career as civil servant. Interviewed by Mary Murphy, September 2, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- JOHN MAXNESS AND LEILA MCPHERSON MAXNESS INTERVIEW, OH 1077; 1 tape(s), Summary 3 pages
  John and Leila Maxness were residents of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s. They discuss living in McCone City; operating a bar with her first husband Tom McPherson; recreation; his work clearing brush. Interviewed by Mary Murphy, August 1, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- ORVILLE SHEFELBINE INTERVIEW, OH 1078; 1 tape(s), Summary 3 pages
  Orville Shefelbine (b. 1914), resident of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s discusses his work clearing brush and building the spillway; Civilian Conservation Corps (CCC) camps; living conditions; recreation; the town of New Deal. Interviewed by Mary Murphy, August 1, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- JAMES WISEMAN AND FLORENCE WISEMAN INTERVIEW, OH 1079; 1 tape(s), Summary 3 pages
  James (b. 1906) and Florence Wiseman, residents of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s, discuss James' work on the railroad, the spillway, and the rigger; and Florence's work in a laundry; living conditions; recreation. Interviewed by Mary Murphy, July 31, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- LINDA KUEBLER SKINNER INTERVIEW, OH 1080; 2 tape(s), Summary 5 pages
  Linda Skinner (b. 1908) was a resident of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s. She discusses her work in a meat market in New Deal; living conditions; recreation; the slide disaster; work in the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers information booth at the dam site. Interviewed by Mary Murphy, July 31, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- EDI G. MASSA SERNEL INTERVIEW, OH 1081; 1 tape(s), Summary 4 pages
  Edi Sernel was a resident of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s. She discusses her childhood in Red Lodge; her work as a telephone operator for the project; living conditions; recreation. Interviewed by Mary Murphy, July 31, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- WILLIAM FLY INTERVIEW, OH 1082; 2 tape(s), Transcript 15 pages
  William Fly (b. 1914) was a resident of Fort Peck, Montana during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s. He discusses his childhood in Laurel, his clerical work on the dam project, barracks life, recreation, the slide disaster. Interviewed by Mary Murphy, July 31, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- ETHELYN "BROWNIE" MASON INTERVIEW, OH 1083; 1 tape(s), Summary 2 pages
  Ethelyn Mason was a resident of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam during the late 1930s. She describes her secretarial work for the project; recreation. Interviewed by Mary Murphy, July 31, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- ALDEN CANTERBURY INTERVIEW, OH 1084; 1 tape(s), Summary 4 pages
  Alden Canterbury (b. 1909) Fort Peck, Montana resident during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam, 1936-1939, discusses his work on the dredge crew and tug boat; living conditions. Interviewed by Mary Murphy, July 30, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- OWEN WILLIAMS INTERVIEW, OH 1085; 2 tape(s), Summary 5 pages
  Owen Williams (b. 1915), a resident of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s describes recreation, barracks life, his work on the dam and the Crow Indian heritage. Interviewed by Rick Duncan, August 1, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- PHILIP GANNON INTERVIEW, OH 1086; 1 tape(s), Summary 3 pages
  Philip Gannon (b. 1916) was a resident of Fort Peck, Montana during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s. He discusses his work as an engineer, a slide disaster, recreation in the area. Interviewed by Rick Duncan, August 2, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- JEROLD VAN FAASEN INTERVIEW, OH 1087; 1 tape(s), Summary 5 pages
  Jerold Van Faasen (b. 1913), a resident of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s, discusses survey and concrete work; living conditions; recreation; his work as an engineer. Interviewed by Rick Duncan, August 3, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- FRED MICHELS INTERVIEW, OH 1088; 1 tape(s), Summary 3 pages
  Fred Michels (b. 1914) was a resident of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s. He discusses working for a Buttrey's store, recreation, wages. Interviewed by Rick Duncan, August 2, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- CLARENCE CRANE INTERVIEW, OH 1089; 1 tape(s), Summary 3 pages
  Clarence Crane (b. 1910) was a resident of Fort Peck, Montana during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s. He discusses stripping work on the dam and living conditions. Interviewed by Rick Duncan, August 1, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- JAMES MONTFORT INTERVIEW, OH 1090; 1 tape(s), Summary 3 pages
  James Montfort (b. 1914), a resident of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s, discusses his work stripping and truck driving, living in Wilson, and recreation. Interviewed by Rick Duncan, August 1, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- HAROLD BRYANT INTERVIEW, OH 1091; 1 tape(s), Summary 3 pages
  Harold Bryant (b. 1920), a Fort Peck, Montana resident during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s, discusses quarry work, living in Park Grove, a slide disaster, recreation in and around Fort Peck. Interviewed by Rick Duncan, July 31, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- JOHN PORTEEN INTERVIEW, OH 1092; 1 tape(s), Summary 3 pages
  John Porteen (b. 1903), a resident of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s, discusses his work on the dam following the slide disaster, living conditions, recreation. Interviewed by Rick Duncan, August 1, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- PETER FRIESEN INTERVIEW, OH 1093; 2 tape(s), Summary 4 pages
  Peter Friesen (b. 1912) of Fort Peck, Montana during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s, discusses his concrete work; training as a welder; recreation; local scarlet fever epidemic. Interviewed by Rick Duncan, July 31, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- MYRON F. "BARNEY" BAKER INTERVIEW, OH 1094; 2 tape(s), Summary 4 pages
  Myron F. "Barney" Baker, Fort Peck, Montana resident, discusses his work in the late 1930s during the Fort Peck Dam construction. He specifically discusses his work truck driving; living in Wheeler; recreation; a slide disaster, and his work in Glasgow. Interviewed by Rick Duncan, July 29, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- WALTER LUSE INTERVIEW, OH 1095; 1 tape(s), Summary 3 pages
  Walter Luse (b. 1907) was a resident of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s. He discusses his work clearing brush; other laboring jobs; the drilling business; a slide disaster. Interviewed by Rick Duncan, July 30, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- TOM MULLEN INTERVIEW, OH 1096; 2 tape(s), Summary 5 pages
  Tom Mullen (b. 1903) a resident of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s, discusses his work in tunnels, pipelines, and Derrick boat. He recalls the slide disaster, working conditions, and recreation. Interviewed by Rick Duncan, July 30, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- EMIL KRAVIK INTERVIEW, OH 1097; 2 tape(s), Summary 4 pages
  Emil Kravik (b. 1919) was a resident of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s. He discusses his work on dredges and pipelines, truck driving, recreation, working conditions. Interviewed by Rick Duncan, July 30, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- JIM WARDLOW INTERVIEW, OH 1098; 1 tape(s), Summary 2 pages
  Jim Wardlow (b. 1906) a resident of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s, discusses living on a houseboat; his work on a drilling crew; flying; recreation. Interviewed by Rick Duncan, July 31, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- GEORGE LARSON INTERVIEW, OH 1099; 1 tape(s), Summary 3 pages
  George Larson (b. 1920) was a resident of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s. He discusses his work on a pipeline, recreation, the slide disaster, working conditions. Interviewed by Diane Sands, August 1, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- RAYMOND HOLDERMAN INTERVIEW, OH 1100; 2 tape(s), Summary 5 pages
  Raymond Holderman (b. 1919) was a resident of Fort Peck, Montana during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s. He discusses his father's work in the state-owned liquor store, recreation, wages, work in the quarry, and the landslide disaster at the dam. Interviewed by Diane Sands, August 1, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- MARGE FITZSIMMONS INTERVIEW, OH 1101; 1 tape(s), Summary 1 pages
  Marge Fitzsimmons (b. 1917) was a resident of Fort Peck, Montana during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s. She discusses her childhood; working in Flaten's dress shop in Glasgow; Buttrey's in Fort Peck; and recreation in the Fort Peck area. Interviewed by Diane Sands, August 1, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- RUBY MORTON MARTIN INTERVIEW, OH 1102; 2 tape(s), Summary 7 pages
  Ruby Martin (b. 1911) was a resident of the Fort Peck, Montana area during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s. She discusses her training and work as a nurse; health care facilities; living in a hotel; recreation; living conditions. Interviewed by Diane Sands, July 31, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- ANTONE GORENC INTERVIEW, OH 1103; 2 tape(s), Summary 4 pages
  Antone Gorenc (b. 1915), a resident of Fort Peck, Montana during the construction of the Fort Peck Dam in the late 1930s discusses his work on construction of the Beartooth Highway; on sawmill and cement crews at the dam; conducting soil tests; and living conditions. Interviewed by Diane Sands, August 2, 1987, Fort Peck, MT.
- RUSSELL STADALMAN INTERVIEW, OH 1104; 1 tape(s), Summary 4 pages
  Russell Stadalman (b. 1915) discusses his experiences with the Civilian Conservation Corps (CCC) in the Alder and Olney areas; describes winter working conditions; construction of a giant water trough; and fire fighting near Elk Lake. He also recounts recreational activities such as boxing and fishing. Interviewed by Mike Korn, July, 9, 1988, Dillon, MT.
- FRED FROEBEL INTERVIEW, OH 1105; 1 tape(s), Summary 7 pages
  Fred Froebel discusses his experiences in the Civilian Conservation Corps (CCC); his job as a canteen steward; recreation and life in Winifred and Lewistown, Montana; local wages. Interviewed by Doni Phillips, July 9, 1988, Dillon, MT.
- SIDNEY D. KEIL INTERVIEW, OH 1106; 1 tape(s), Summary 8 pages
  Sidney Keil (b. 1917), a North Dakota native, joined the Civilian Conservation Corps (CCC) in 1935 and was stationed in North Dakota, Washington, and Minnesota and enlisted in the U.S. Army in 1941. Keil discusses life in the CCC camps and his work there. Interviewed by Doni M. Phillips, July 9, 1988, Dillon, MT.
- HERBERT JACOBSON INTERVIEW, OH 1107; 1 tape(s), Transcript 28 pages